You need to enable JavaScript to run this app.

### Bad Panda Inc. Privacy Policy

Last updated December 19, 2019
------------------------------

This privacy policy describes how Bad Panda, Inc. and its related companies, collect, use and share personal information of consumer users of www.gifyourgame.com (the “Site”). This Policy also applies to any of our other websites that post this Policy. This Policy does not apply to websites that post different policies.
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**WHAT WE COLLECT**  
  
We get information about you in a range of ways.  
  
**Information You Give Us.**  
  
We collect your‎ email address, username, password, the gifs you create with us, as well as other information you directly give us on our Site or through contests that we run.  
  
**Information We Get From Others.**  
  
We may get information about you from other sources. We may add this to information we get from this Site.  
  
**Information Automatically Collected.**  
  
We automatically log information about you and your computer. For example, when visiting our Site, we log your computer operating system type, browser type, browser language, the website(s) you visited before browsing to our Site, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, access times, information about your use of and actions on our Site and, when you use our desktop client, games played on your computer.  
  
**Cookies.**  
  
We may log information using "cookies." Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. This type of information is collected to make the Site more useful to you and to tailor the experience with us to meet your interests and needs. There are a many tools available that allow you to control and delete cookies through your browser settings and through third party providers.  
  
**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  

We may use your personal information as follows:  
  
We may use your personal information to operate, maintain, and improve our Site, and deliver products, and services.  
  
We may use your personal information to process and deliver contest related information.  
  
We may use your personal information to respond to questions and generally to provide customer service and support.  
  
We may use your personal information to send information including confirmations, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and administrative messages.  
  
We may use your personal information to communicate about promotions, upcoming events, contests, and other news about products and services offered by us and our selected partners.  
  
We may use your personal information to protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.  

**SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may share personal information as follows:  
  
We may share personal information with your consent. For example, you may let us share personal information with others for their own marketing uses. Those uses will be subject to their privacy policies.  
  
We may share personal information when we are engaged in a negotiation involving the sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets. These negotiations can include any merger, financing, acquisition, or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding.  
  
We may share personal information for legal, protection, and safety purposes.  
  
We may share information to comply with laws.  
  
We may share information to respond to lawful requests and legal processes.  
  
We may share information to protect the rights and intellectual property of Bad Panda, Inc., our agents, users, partners, and others. This includes enforcing our agreements, policies, and terms of use.  
  
We may share information in an emergency. This includes protecting the safety of our employees and agents, our users, or any person.  
  
We may share information with those who need it to do work for us.  
  
We may also share aggregated and/or anonymized data.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**  
  
The Site does not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you believe we are inappropriately processing personal information of a minor, the parent or legal guardian of the minor can request that we delete any information that we may have about the minor by contacting us at any time.  
  
**INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES**  
  
You may send requests about personal information using our contact information below. You can request to change contact choices, opt-out of our sharing with others, update your personal information, or delete your personal information as required by applicable law.  
  
You can typically remove and reject cookies from our Site with your browser settings. Many browsers are set to accept cookies until you change your settings. If you remove or reject our cookies, it could affect how our Site works for you.  
  
If we send marketing emails, they will tell you how to “opt-out” or “unsubscribe.” If you opt out, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails may include emails about your accounts or our business dealings with you such as customer or technical support and information related to contests.  
  
**CONTACT INFORMATION.**  
  
Comments or questions regarding this privacy policy can be sent to our address below:  
  
Bad Panda, Inc.  
1540 7th Street  
Suite 300  
Santa Monica, California 90401  
support@gifyourgame.com  
  
**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**  
  
We may change this privacy policy from time to time. If we make any changes, we will change the Last Updated date below.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Parsing Replay

Clips Rendering

Hooray! We're making your clips now and will take a few minutes. When complete you'll be able to find them in your clip library and can share them with your friends.

OkayView in Clip Library

Oh No!

CloseOK

Error

CloseOK

Create Private Tag

Private tags make it easy to filter your clips library

CancelCreate
